There are a few bugs in Solar Fire that need to be worked around in order to create a correct calendar with Moon Void of Course calculated correctly.

For March, must do in two separate batches, split at DST day, same for Nov.

For DST months, do ical export with PST setting, auto DST in solarfire.  Do everything except moon
ingress and moon voids..... do those special next.

For MOON voids and ingress: RUN VOID MOON FOR NEVADA STANDARD TIME - 7.  THEY WILL BE 
CORRECT FOR BOTH PDT AND PST.   
generate ical file in Solar Fire.  Do all time zone stuff manually.  Moon quarters will be wrong during DST.

move cal file to code dir on Mac

change filename to SFCAL.ics
run new.pl in code dir
take the -b file, and run the Calendar macro in Word -cnt-opt-c

upload to test cal first

run void of course stuff second -VOC has to be separate, just skip for the Greenwich calendar.  voids are wrong in DST only.
RUN VOID MOON FOR NEVADA STANDARD TIME.  THEY WILL BE CORRECT FOR BOTH PDT AND PST.

remove 1st, 2nd, 3rd and Full Moon (time is one hour off during DST)

Fix all stations - Look for R and D and make Retrograde and Direct

redo voids (VOC or VC)  for one hour later and import separately
    didn't need to do one hour later for PDT in fall.   Do only moon to moon aspects,
   with not actual aspects.  click VOC etc on.

RUN VOID MOON FOR NEVADA STANDARD TIME.  THEY WILL BE CORRECT FOR BOTH PDT AND PST.


GMT calendar - do in GMT on solar fire, set time zone to Greenwich Mean Time GMT

on Google go to General Settings and set my time zone for Greenwich GMT no dst. then do import.  Should match.  

Don't do Voids.  do them separate.  Run file through word with macro to fix up for calendar.  Remove all "first quarter moon" stuff by hand.  test first, then import into GMT calendar when perfect.  make sure test calendars are all for GMT greenwich no DST too.  When running macro, first put file in Desktop/code and run new.pl on it from the terminal.  Then run Word macro on it.  Normal template must be in right location for macro to run.  see instructions.txt in code folder.

If calendar won't import because duplicate entries already updloaded - change the UID.

Use Chrome calendar Bulk action tool to remove dupes.  Must be done from Chrome.
http://vps26060.ovh.net/gcalendarcleaner/?code=4/0gBHqcsWhN-McWVGLUQE-NO2qj3F.glQN07R_qH0YEnp6UAPFm0GOpc5ujwI

To download an archive:  go to gmail, account settings, etc.

